Hello friends, welcome to
our
YouTube2. In today's video, we are going to
tell you how to log in to the ICICI Potential
Life Insurance app if you have taken any
insurance or term plan or any
savings plan from ICICI Potential Life Insurance.
How will
you be able to see your fund details or your policy
and how can you manage it.
You can change the nominee name,
switch the fund, you
can see and change every information in your ICICI Potential Life Insurance app.
So let's start the video.
For that, first of all you will have to download this
ICICI Potential Life Insurance application from the Play Store.
After downloading, when you open it, an
interface like this appears.
You will need some permissions here, so
you will allow that permission. You
can click on Next here.
Otherwise, you can click on Skip. So let's go to
Next. So, we are telling you that
you can control your policy 24*7. You
can control it.  You
can pay your premium, download statements,
monitor all your policies. You
can monitor all your policies in a single app.
By buying new life insurance, you
can also buy a new policy. So let's
skip here by clicking next. So,
see here, you
also need permission for your camera for video recording. So,
you can do that on the 'using' tab.
Whatever mic access you have, you will give it access.
Now let's come back here.
After that, if we are asking for location permission, you will
also give location permission. Look,
its window will come up like this.
After that, you will get the option to sign up and login here. If
you are doing it for the first time, then
you will sign up here and
fill up your details. After that, for the
first time, here you will have to enter your
mobile number. You can log in in three ways:
mobile number and date of birth, email
ID and date of birth and policy number and date
of birth. So, by entering your email
ID and date of birth or mobile number,
you will log in here. So,
as I enter my details here, I get
logged in.  Look here, I
entered my mobile number here and the
OTP came here, now I have to enter the OTP,
after entering the OTP, you will see here the
option of set new password will come,
you will enter your new password here,
after that you will have to click on confirm here,
so I create a new password,
after that you will click on OK
here, see here your password has been
updated successfully, after that OK, after that
you have to create a four digit MPIN here, so
as I
set a four digit MPIN here, after that
after entering the four digit PIN here you have to click on confirm, see it is done,
after that you are being asked to
put your fingerprint also, so you
can click on fingerprint, after that
your phone window will
open here like this, now here you will see
your insurance cover, your life
cover, whatever it is, here you will see on top, so you
will click on view details on it, then all
your life kar is also being shown here,
whatever policy you have taken, it will be shown there as well  You will
see this, after that you
will click on my policy here, then it will also be
visible here that
how many policies you have taken from IC Potential,
one, two, three, four, whatever,
here you have active two policies in
active date, there is none and two are lying in active,
so you can see it here and if
you have also taken any investment plan, then
you will simply
click on fund value here and select the policy,
whatever it is, you will be
able to see it here simply, the complete details of yours, that is, how much have
we invested, what is the fund
value, how much are you getting in return now
and what is the gain, in which funds are
your payments invested,
after that
you will be able to check your details here by clicking on my profile,
after clicking on my policy,
if you want to make some changes in your ongoing policy, then
you will simply
click on my policy here, after that see here the
policy details will appear, check the policy details,
you have to do some financial transaction  If you
have to do any transaction, update
bank, switch or check fund value,
premium redirection, health
direction, whatever you have to do or
pay premium,
you can see it here.
After going to profile, you can update nominee,
whatever details of nominee you can change it, my
profile and you can also see the information of your agent,
through which agents we have
taken this policy, their complete details will be available here
and here you
need statement, receipt of premium paid by you,
premium notice, TDS certificate,
loan statement, you will be able to see all those things, by going to other
you
get other services here, settlement option,
medical report, you will get all these things, so I hope
you liked today's video, if you liked the video then
like and
share it, see you in the next video, till then
thank you